(this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz-app"]||[]).push([[6],{36:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.d(a,"a",(function(){return s}));var n=t(37);function s(e,a){if(e){if("string"===typeof e)return Object(n.a)(e,a);var t=Object.prototype.toString.call(e).slice(8,-1);return"Object"===t&&e.constructor&&(t=e.constructor.name),"Map"===t||"Set"===t?Array.from(e):"Arguments"===t||/^(?:Ui|I)nt(?:8|16|32)(?:Clamped)?Array$/.test(t)?Object(n.a)(e,a):void 0}}},37:function(e,a,t){"use strict";function n(e,a){(null==a||a>e.length)&&(a=e.length);for(var t=0,n=new Array(a);t<a;t++)n[t]=e[t];return n}t.d(a,"a",(function(){return n}))},38:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.d(a,"a",(function(){return s}));var n=t(36);function s(e,a){return function(e){if(Array.isArray(e))return e}(e)||function(e,a){if("undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.iterator in Object(e)){var t=[],n=!0,s=!1,r=void 0;try{for(var i,o=e[Symbol.iterator]();!(n=(i=o.next()).done)&&(t.push(i.value),!a||t.length!==a);n=!0);}catch(u){s=!0,r=u}finally{try{n||null==o.return||o.return()}finally{if(s)throw r}}return t}}(e,a)||Object(n.a)(e,a)||function(){throw new TypeError("Invalid attempt to destructure non-iterable instance.\nIn order to be iterable, non-array objects must have a [Symbol.iterator]() method.")}()}},39:function(e,a,t){"use strict";var n=t(1);t(0);a.a=function(e){var a=e.message,t=e.alertClassType;return Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:"alert alert-dismissible fade show ".concat(t),role:"alert",children:[a,Object(n.jsx)("button",{type:"button",className:"btn-close","data-bs-dismiss":"alert","aria-label":"Close"})]})}},40:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.d(a,"c",(function(){return n})),t.d(a,"b",(function(){return s})),t.d(a,"a",(function(){return r}));var n=[{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0990996"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"093909"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"009039"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"090089"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"01010101"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"092299"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"986709999"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222099EAS"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"2222099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09922099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222292099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0998999099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09909999343"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09909999999999"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0990999999943"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09459099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0912219099"}],s=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:5;return Promise.resolve(n.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e))},r=Object.freeze([{_id:"5c8a1d5b0190b214360dc057",name:"Jonas Schmedtmann",email:"admin@example.com",role:"admin",password:"123456"},{_id:"5c8a1dfa2f8fb814b56fa181",name:"Lourdes Browning",email:"loulou@example.com",role:"user",password:"123456"},{_id:"5c8a1e1a2f8fb814b56fa182",name:"Sophie Louise Hart",email:"sophie@example.com",role:"user",password:"123456"}])},47:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.r(a);var n=t(1),s=t(38),r=t(0),i=t(39),o=t(40),u=t(11);a.default=function(e){var a=e.location,t=e.history,c=Object(r.useState)(""),l=Object(s.a)(c,2),d=l[0],h=l[1],p=Object(r.useState)(""),m=Object(s.a)(p,2),b=m[0],v=m[1],f=Object(r.useState)(""),y=Object(s.a)(f,2),k=y[0],w=y[1],j=a.search?a.search.split("=")[1]:"/react-quiz-app/questions";return Object(r.useEffect)((function(){var e=Object(u.b)("authUserInfo")?Object(u.b)("authUserInfo"):{};Object.keys(e).length>0&&t.push(j)}),[j,t]),Object(n.jsx)("main",{className:"form-signin-contain vh-100",children:Object(n.jsxs)("form",{className:"form-signin text-center",onSubmit:function(e){e.preventDefault(),d&&b?!function(e,a){var t=o.a.find((function(t){return t.email===e&&t.password===a}));return!!t&&(Object(u.c)("authUserInfo",{email:e,id:t._id,role:t.role}),!0)}(d,b)?w("User not match!"):(w(""),t.push("/react-quiz-app/questions")):w("Email and passwor is required!")},children:[k&&k?Object(n.jsx)(i.a,{message:k,alertClassType:"alert-danger"}):null,Object(n.jsx)("h1",{className:"h3 mb-3 fw-normal",children:"Please sign in"}),Object(n.jsx)("label",{htmlFor:"inputEmail",className:"visually-hidden",children:"Email address"}),Object(n.jsx)("input",{type:"email",id:"inputEmail",className:"form-control",placeholder:"Email address",required:!0,autoFocus:!0,value:d,onChange:function(e){return h(e.target.value)}}),Object(n.jsx)("label",{htmlFor:"inputPassword",className:"visually-hidden",children:"Password"}),Object(n.jsx)("input",{type:"password",id:"inputPassword",className:"form-control",placeholder:"Password",required:!0,value:b,onChange:function(e){return v(e.target.value)}}),Object(n.jsx)("button",{className:"w-100 btn btn-lg btn-primary",type:"submit",children:"Sign in"}),Object(n.jsx)("p",{className:"mt-5 mb-3 text-muted",children:"\xa9 2020-2021"})]})})}}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=6.56753bdc.chunk.js.map